Guide to the Western Filmscript Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Western Filmscripts Acquired After July 1996, 1917-2008
  - The Proud Ones, 1955 December 5 (Box 110)
  - The Proud Ones, 1955 August 10 (Box 110)
  - Proud River, undated (Box 110)
  - Pursuit [Dirty Mary and Crazy Larry], 1973 September 4 (Box 110)
  - Quantez, 1957 February 20 (Box 110)
  - Queen of the Yukon, [1940] (Box 110)
  - The Quick and the Dead, [1995] (Box 110)
  - Quiet Cool, 1986 February 27 (Box 110)
  - Racing with the Moon, 1983 April 4 (Box 111)
  - Racketeers of the Range, 1939 (Box 111)
  - Radar Patrol vs. Spy King, 1949 September 1 (Box 140)
  - Rafferty and the Gold Dust Twins, 1973 October 17 (Box 111)
  - Rafferty and the Gold Dust Twins [two copies], 1973 October 29; 2 (Box 111)
  - The Rage, 1965 October 20 (Box 111)
  - The Rage, 1965 (Box 111)
  - The Rage, 1971 August 27 (Box 111)
  - The Rage [two copies], 1971 September 28; 2 (Box 111)
  - The Raggedy Man, [circa 1976] (Box 111)
  - The Raggedy Man, 1977 June 29 (Box 111)
  - The Raggedy Man, 1980 April 30 (Box 111)
  - Raiders, 1963 November 14 (Box 111)
  - Raiders, 1963 (Box 111)
  - Raiders of Ghost City [chapters 1-13], 1944; 13 (Box 111)
  - Raiders of the Range [two copies], 1942 January 23; 2 (Box 112)
  - The Rainbow Trail [two copies], 1931 September 28; 2 (Box 112)
  - Rainbow Warrior [On Deadly Ground], 1992 December 2 (Box 112)
  - Ramona, 1935 July 9 (Box 112)
  - Range Busters Picture II, [circa 1940] (Box 112)
  - Range Rogues, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Range Rogues, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Range Rogues [Brand of Fear], [1949] (Box 112)
  - The Ranger, the Cook and a Hole in the Sky, 1944 June 27 (Box 112)
  - Rangers of Fortune, 1940 August 8 (Box 112)
  - Rangers of Fortune, 1940 August 16 (Box 112)
  - The Rangers Ride, [1948] (Box 112)
  - The Rare Breed, 1965 November 22 (Box 112)
  - Ravenous, 1996 December 13 (Box 112)
  - Raw Edge, 1955 April 27 (Box 112)
  - Raw Edge, 1965 March 30 (Box 112)
  - Rawhide (Subtitle: Incident of the Rusty Shotgun), 1963 August 27 (Box 112)
  - The Rawhide Breed [The Rawhide Trail], 1957 September 1 (Box 112)
  - Rawhide Rangers, 1941 June 10 (Box 112)
  - Rawhide Trail, [circa 1948] (Box 112)
  - The Rawhide Years, 1955 August 17 (Box 112)
  - Ready for the Tiger, 1970 March 17 (Box 113)
  - Ready to Ride, 1950 March 3 (Box 113)
  - Rebel in the Town, 1954 November 18 (Box 113)
  - Rebel in Town, 1955 December 21 (Box 113)
  - Rebel Rousers, 1970 March 31 (Box 113)
  - Red Blizzard [Pawnee], 1952 July 15 (Box 137)
  - Red Canyon [two copies], 1948 December 6; 2 (Box 113)
  - Red Heat [Tell Them Willie Boy is Here], 1969 May 27 (Box 113)
  - Red Prado, [circa 1965] (Box 113)
  - The Red Rider [chapters 13-15], 1934 (Box 113)
  - Red River, 1987 November 6 (Box 113)
  - Red River Riders [The Range Busters], [1940] (Box 113)
  - Red River Riders, 1942 (Box 113)
  - Red River Shore, 24 August 1953 (Box 113)
  - Red Rock West, 1991 July (Box 113)
  - Red Ryder [Marshall of Reno], 1944 March 6 (Box 113)
  - Red Sundown, 1955 June 6 (Box 113)
  - Redskin, 1928 August 23 (Box 113)
  - Renegade, [circa 1955] (Box 113)
  - Renegade Roundup [Rustlers of the Badlands], 1944 June 6 (Box 113)
  - Renfrew Rides North [Renfrew on the Great White Trail], [1938] (Box 113)
  - Reno Brothers, 1956 August 20 (Box 114)
  - Reprisal, 1956 March 5 (Box 114)
  - Retroactive, 1966 February 6 (Box 114)
  - The Return of a Man Called Horse, 1975 September 22 (Box 114)
  - Return of the Outlaw, [circa 1950] (Box 114)
  - Return of the Outlaw [The Parson and the Outlaw], [circa 1957] (Box 114)
  - Return to Lonesome Dove: Part One [The Vision], 1993 June 5 (Box 114)
  - Return to Lonesome Dove: Part One [The Vision], 1993 June 17 (Box 114)
  - Return to Lonesome Dove: Part Three [The Legacy], 1993 June 17 (Box 114)
  - Return to Lonesome Dove: Part Two [The Forge], 1993 June 17 (Box 114)
  - The Revengers, [circa 1969] (Box 114)
  - The Revengers, 1971 January 5 (Box 114)
  - The Reward, 1964 April 13 (Box 114)
  - The Reward, 1964 May 22 (Box 114)
  - The Reward, 1964 June 8 (Box 114)
  - Rhythm on the Range, 1936 March 7 (Box 114)
  - Rhythm on the Range, 1936 March 24 (Box 114)
  - Rhythm on the Range, 1936 July 15 (Box 114)
  - Ricochet Romance [The Matchmaker], 1954 January 18 (Box 114)
  - Richocet Romance, 1954 May 26 (Box 114)
  - Ride a Crooked Mile, 1938 November 7 (Box 114)
  - Ride a Crooked Trail, 1958 January 24 (Box 114)
  - Ride a Crooked Trail, trailer, 1958 March 14 (Box 114)
  - The Ride Back, [1957] (Box 114)
  - Ride Clear of Diablo, 1953 November 11 (Box 115)
  - Ride Kelly Ride, 1940 November 28 (Box 115)
  - Ride Kelly Ride, 1940 November 28 (Box 115)
  - Ride on, Vaquero, 1940 December 7 (Box 115)
  - Ride Out for Revenge, 1957 February 7 (Box 115)
  - Ride Ranger Ride, [1936] (Box 115)
  - Ride, Tenderfoot, Ride, [1940] (Box 115)
  - Ride the West Wind, 1954 August 6 (Box 115)
  - Rider of Death Valley, 1932 (Box 115)
  - Riders of Death Valley [trailer, chapters 1-15], 1940; 17 (Box 115)
  - Riders of Death Valley [trailer, chapters 1-15], 1941; 16 (Box 115)
  - Riders of Pasco Basin, 1939 October 24 (Box 116)
  - Riders of the Mystery Mountain, 1940 (Box 116)
  - Riders of the Rio Grande, 1943 February 15 (Box 116)
  - Riders of the Santa Fe, trailer, 1944 August 30 (Box 116)
  - Riders on the Range [Silver on the Sage], 1938 September 13 (Box 116)
  - Riding High, 1942 December 12 (Box 116)
  - Riding High, 1943 August 10 (Box 116)
  - The Riding Kid, 1951 April 9 (Box 116)
  - The Riding Kid, 1951 April 10 (Box 116)
  - The Riding Kid, 1951 August 21 (Box 116)
  - The Riding Kid, 1951 December 7 (Box 116)
  - The Riding Kid, 1952 February 18 (Box 116)
  - Riding the High Country, 1955 June 29 (Box 116)
  - Rimfire, 1949 February 14 (Box 116)
  - Rin Tin Tin, 1994 April 18 (Box 116)
  - Rio Grande Roundup [Texas Stampede], 1938 October 12 (Box 116)
  - River Lady, 1947 February 15 (Box 116)
  - River Lady, 1947 July 11 (Box 116)
  - River Lady, 1948 January 27 (Box 116)
  - The Road, 2008 (Box 140)
    Includes production notes.
  - The Road to Reno, 1931 August 28 (Box 116)
  - The Road to Reno, 1931 September 29 (Box 116)
  - The Road to Reno, 1931 October 6 (Box 116)
  - The Road to Reno, 1938 August 25 (Box 116)
  - The Road to Reno, Part One, 1938 (Box 116)
  - Roaring Range [Shadows on the Range], 1946 (Box 116)
  - The Roaring West [chapters 1-15], 1935; 15 (Box 117)
  - Robbers' Roost, 1932 August 24 (Box 117)
  - Robin Hood of Texas, [1947] (Box 117)
  - Robin Hood of the Range, 1942 June 11 (Box 117)
  - Rock Radio is American Graffiti: (saga of the low riders) [American Graffiti], 1972 May 10 (Box 140)
  - Rollin' Along [Drifting Along], 1945 September 17 (Box 117)
  - Romance of the Rio Grande, 1929 August 6 (Box 117)
  - Rooster Cogburn, 1974 August 26 (Box 117)
  - Rose of the Ranch, 1935 December 13 (Box 117)
  - Rough Night in Jericho, 1966 Septmber 23 (Box 117)
  - The Rough Riders, undated (Box 117)
  - Round Up, 1941 February 21 (Box 117)
  - Roy Rogers, 1939 September 18 (Box 117)
  - The Royal Mounted Rides Again, 1945 July 1 (Box 117)
  - The Royal Mounted Rides Again [chapters 1-13], 1945; 13 (Box 117)
  - The Royal Mounted Rides Again [chapters 1-13], 1945; 13 (Box 118)
  - Ruby, 1991 May 28 (Box 118)
  - Ruby Ridge: Night One & Night Two, 1996 (Box 140)
  - Ruggles of Red Gap, 1934 October 11 (Box 118)
  - Ruggles of Red Gap, 1935 January 28 (Box 118)
  - Run for Cover, 1954 March 29 (Box 118)
  - Running the Big Wild Red, 1973 March 5 (Box 118)
  - Rush, 1991 February 27 (Box 118)
  - Rush, 1992 March 10 (Box 118)
  - Rustler's Round Up, 1945 December 1 (Box 118)
  - Rustler's Round Up, 1946 August 17 (Box 118)
  - The Rustlers of Red Dog [chapters 1-12], 1934 (Box 118)
  - Rustlers' Ransom, 1950 January 31 (Box 118)
  - Sacred Ground, 1980 March 17 (Box 119)
  - Saddle Brigade [Fort Siege], 1967 April 26 (Box 119)
  - Saddle Serenade [Cowboy Cavalier], [1948] (Box 119)
  - Saddle Serenade [Cowboy Cavalier], [1948] (Box 119)
  - Saddle Tramp [Fiddle-Foot], 1950 (Box 119)
  - Saddle Tramp, 1950 June 29 (Box 119)
  - The Saga of Hemp Brown, 1957 July 18 (Box 119)
  - The Saga of Hemp Brown, 1958 January 16 (Box 119)
  - Sailor's Luck, 1933 January 14 (Box 119)
  - Sam Bass and Calamity Jane, 1948 August 16 (Box 119)
  - Sam Bass and Calamity Jane, 1948 September 13 (Box 119)
  - Sam Hill, 1970 September 24 (Box 119)
  - San Antonio, 1944 June 29 (Box 119)
  - Sand, 1975 Aug 7 (Box 137)
  - Santa Cruz, 1964 (Box 119)
  - Santa Fe Scouts, 1943 January 28 (Box 119)
  - Santa Fe Stampede, 1938 September 26 (Box 119)
  - Santa Fe Trail, 1940 July 2 (Box 119)
  - Santa Fe Uprising, 1946 February 25 (Box 119)
  - Savage, 1995 April 5 (Box 119)
  - Savage Eye, 1958 (Box 119)
  - The Scalphunters, 1968 February 15 (Box 119)
  - Scarecrow, 1972 (Box 140)
  - The Scarlet Horseman [chapters 1-13], 1945 September-October (Box 120)
  - The Scarlet Horseman [chapters 1-13], 1945 December-March (Box 120)
  - Search for the Gods, 1974 October 8 (Box 120)
  - The Second Greatest Sex, 1954 November 2 (Box 120)
  - The Secret of Convict Lake, 1951 January 5 (Box 120)
  - The Seekers, Part One [two copies], 1978 November 30; 2 (Box 120)
  - The Seekers, Part Two, 1978 December 6 (Box 120)
  - Seminole, 1953 January 5 (Box 120)
  - The Serial, 1978 (Box 140)
  - Seven Cities of Gold, 1955 February 21 (Box 120)
  - Seven Ways from Sundown, 1960 August 4 (Box 120)
  - Seventh Cavalry [The Return of Custer], 1956 January 7 (Box 120)
  - Shadow of a Gun, circa 1955 (Box 120)
  - The Shadow Riders, 1982 March 22 (Box 120)
  - Shadows on the Sage, 1942 June 24 (Box 120)
  - Shalako, circa 1969 (Box 120)
  - Shane, 1951 July 18 (Box 121)
  - She Was a Lady, 1934 May 19 (Box 121)
  - She Went to the Races, 1945 April 17 (Box 121)
  - The Sheriff, 1970 December 2 (Box 121)
  - Sheriff of Wichita, 1948 (Box 121)
  - Shotgun, 1954 August 4 (Box 138)
  - Shotgun, 1954 September 23 (Box 140)
  - Shoot Out, 1970 October 2 (Box 121)
  - Showdown, 1972 March 1 (Box 121)
  - Showdown, 1972 April 3 (Box 121)
  - Showdown at Abilene, 1956 February 9 (Box 121)
  - Sierra, 1950 January 16 (Box 121)
  - Sierra Express, 1940-1941 (Box 121)
  - Silence of the North, 1977 February 16 (Box 121)
  - The Silent Gun, 1969 June 26 (Box 121)
  - Silent Tongue, 1991 June (Box 121)
  - The Silver Bullet, [1942] (Box 121)
  - Silver Butte, 1949 July 6 (Box 121)
  - Silver Trails, [1948] (Box 121)
  - Silverado, 1984 October 5 (Box 121)
  - Sin Town, 1942 September 19 (Box 121)
  - Sin Town, 1942 August 7 (Box 121)
  - Sin Town, undated (Box 121)
  - Sin Town, undated (Box 122)
  - The Singing Hill, [1941] (Box 122)
  - The Singing Sheriff, 1944 August 11 (Box 122)
  - The Singing Vagabond, [1935] (Box 122)
  - The Single Spur, circa 1958 (Box 122)
  - Sinola [Joe Kidd], undated (Box 122)
  - Siringo, 1994 April 27 (Box 122)
  - Sister Aimee [Disappearance of Aimee], 1976 June 16 (Box 122)
  - Sitting Bull, undated (Box 137)
  - Six Black Horses, 1961 November 29 (Box 122)
  - Six Pack, 1981 November 23 (Box 122)
  - Six Pack, 1982 January 11 (Box 122)
  - Skin Game, 1969 August 4 (Box 122)
  - Skin Game, 1973 October 2 (Box 122)
  - Slaughter's Trail [Cutter's Trail], 1968 May 31 (Box 122)
  - Sleep All Winter [The Showdown], 1950 January 6 (Box 122)
  - Slim Carter, 1957 July 12 (Box 122)
  - Smoke Signal, 1954 November 30 (Box 122)
  - Smokey, 1945 July 7 (Box 138)
  - Smokey and the Bandit, 1977 April 25 (Box 122)
  - Smokey and the Bandit II [two copies], 1979 December 19; 2 (Box 122)
  - Smokey is the Bandit, 1982 September 27 (Box 122)
  - Smokey is the Bandit, 1982 October 21 (Box 122)
  - Smoky, 1933 August 16 (Box 122)
  - Smoky, 1966 February 18 (Box 122)
  - So This is London, 1930 February 22 (Box 122)
  - Son of Roaring Dan, 1940 July 13 (Box 123)
  - Son of Slade, 1955 May 26 (Box 123)
  - Son of the Morning Star, 1990 March 12 (Box 123)
  - Son of the Morning Star, 1990 April 12 (Box 123)
  - A Song for You [Honeysuckle Rose], 1979 August 30 (Box 123)
  - Song of the Drifter, [1948] (Box 123)
  - The Sons of Katie Elder, 1964 December 24 (Box 123)
  - Spawn of the North, 1937 November 16 (Box 123)
  - Spawn of the North, 1938 February 21 (Box 123)
  - Spawn of the North, 1938 July 23 (Box 123)
  - Spawn of the North, 1938 August 3 (Box 123)
  - Spawn of the North, 1938 August 18 (Box 123)
  - Spencer's Mountain, 1962 June 11 (Box 123)
  - The Spoilers, 1942 January 9 (Box 123)
  - The Spoilers, 1954 July 1 (Box 123)
  - The Spoilers, 1955 January 19 (Box 123)
  - The Spoilers, 1955 July 15 (Box 123)
  - Springtime in the Rockies, [1937] (Box 123)
  - Squelch, 1999 April 28 (Box 123)
  - Stage to Blue River, 1951 September 14 (Box 124)
  - Stage to Chino, 1940 April 30 (Box 137)
  - Stagecoach Express, 1941 December 10 (Box 124)
  - Stagecoach to Denver, 1946 April 4 (Box 124)
  - Stagecoach to Fury, 1956 April 20 (Box 124)
  - The Stalking Moon, 1968 November 1 (Box 124)
  - Stampede [The Conquering Horde], 1930 October 10 (Box 124)
  - Star in the Dust, 1956 February 7 (Box 124)
  - The Stars Fell on Henrietta, 1993 June 1 (Box 124)
  - Stay Away, Joe, 1957 October 16 (Box 124)
  - Stick, 1983 August 5 (Box 124)
  - Stick to Your Guns, 1941 September 17 (Box 124)
  - Stormy, 1935 (Box 124)
  - The Stranger from Ponca City, 1946 October 15 (Box 124)
  - Streets of Laredo, 1948 January 6 (Box 124)
  - Streets of Laredo, 1949 January 24 (Box 124)
  - Streets of Laredo, 1994 October 1 (Box 124)
  - The Streets of Laredo, Part One, 1994 June 1 (Box 124)
  - The Streets of Laredo, Part Two, undated (Box 124)
  - The Streets of Laredo, Part Three, undated (Box 124)
  - The Strip, 1950 October 31 (Box 124)
  - Suddenly, undated (Box 125)
  - The Sullivans, 1943 August 27 (Box 138)
  - Sundown Jim, 1941 December 27 (Box 125)
  - Sundown Kid, 1942 September 23 (Box 125)
  - Sunset, 1986 September 19 (Box 125)
  - Sunset, 1987 March 20 (Box 125)
  - Sunset in Wyoming, [1941] (Box 125)
  - Sunset Pass, 1928 October 31 (Box 125)
  - Sunset Pass, 1933 March 20 (Box 125)
  - Sunset Pass, 1933 April 8 (Box 125)
  - Sunset Pass, 1933 May 7 (Box 125)
  - Sunset Pass, 1933 May 11 (Box 125)
  - Support Your Local Sheriff, 1968 January 15 (Box 125)
  - Support Your Local Sheriff, 1968 November 29 (Box 125)
  - Susannah, 1939 January 24 (Box 125)
  - Sutter's Gold, 1935 October 30 (Box 125)
  - Sutter's Gold, 1936 (Box 125)
  - Sutter's Gold [added scenes], 1936 (Box 125)
  - Swoger's Mules, 1960 October 9 (Box 125)
  - Tales of the Texas Rangers: Double Edge, 1955 July 21 (Box 126)
  - Tall in the Saddle, 1943 May 27 (Box 126)
  - The Tall Men, 1955 January 10 (Box 126)
  - The Tall Men, 1955 February 12 (Box 126)
  - The Tall Men, 1955 March 7 (Box 126)
  - Tall Tale, 1993 July 23 (Box 126)
  - The Tall Texan, 1952 September 20 (Box 126)
  - Tennessee's Partner, 1955 September 1 (Box 126)
  - Tennessee's Partner, 1955 (Box 126)
  - Tenting Tonight on the Old Camp Ground, 1942 September 15 (Box 126)
  - Tequila Sunrise, 1987 June 19 (Box 126)
  - Terms of Endearment, 1981 March (Box 126)
  - Tex, 1981 March 26 (Box 126)
  - The Texans, 1981 June 1 (Box 126)
  - Texas, 1986 April 7 (Box 126)
  - Texas, Brooklyn and Heaven, 1947 August 28 (Box 126)
  - Texas Lady, [circa 1955] (Box 126)
  - A Texas Legend, 1980 October 14 (Box 126)
  - The Texas Picture [Places in the Heart], 1983 September 14; 2 (Box 126)
  - Texas Rangers, 1950 August 15 (Box 126)
  - The Texas Rangers, 1979 (Box 140)
  - Texas Wildcats, [circa 1939] (Box 126)
  - Texasville, 1988 September 20 (Box 127)
  - Texasville, 1988 August 18 (Box 127)
  - Thelma and Louise, 1989 June (Box 127)
  - Thelma and Louise, 1990 April 4 (Box 127)
  - They Shoot Horses, Don't They?, 1969 March 3 (Box 127)
  - Three Desperate Men, 1950 August 31 (Box 127)
  - Three Desperate Men, 1950 December 14 (Box 127)
  - Three Hours to Kill, 1954 January 16 (Box 127)
  - Three Violent People, 1956 October 23 (Box 127)
  - Three Violent People, [1956] (Box 127)
  - Thunder in the Sun, 1959 February 9 (Box 127)
  - Thunder Over the Plains [Come On, Texas], 1952 August 5 (Box 138)
  - Thunder Run, 1984 October 23 (Box 127)
  - Thunder Run, 1985 January 10 (Box 127)
  - The Thunderbird [This Woman is Mine] [two copies], 1941 May 6; 2 (Box 127)
  - Thunderhead, 1944 March 31 (Box 127)
  - Thunderhead, 1944 May 5 (Box 127)
  - Thunderheart, 1991 April 12 (Box 127)
  - Thundering Trails, 1942 Oct 15 (Box 127)
  - A Ticket to Tomahawk, 1949 June 20 (Box 128)
  - Timber Trail, 1947 November 7 (Box 128)
  - Tin Star, 1957 June 10 (Box 128)
  - Tom Mix, 1969 March 26 (Box 128)
  - Tomahawk, 1947 October 27 (Box 128)
  - Tomahawk, 1948 July 21 (Box 128)
  - Tomahawk, 1949 April 22 (Box 128)
  - Tomahawk, 1949 August 23 (Box 128)
  - Tomahawk, 1950 April 14 (Box 128)
  - Tomahawk, 1950 April 14 (Box 140)
  - Tombstone, 1992 November 5 (Box 128)
  - Tombstone, 1993 January 30 (Box 128)
  - Tombstone, 1993 March 15 (Box 128)
  - Tombstone, 1993 March 18 (Box 128)
  - Tombstone, 1993 June 24 (Box 128)
  - Tombstone, 1993 June 29 (Box 128)
  - Tombstone, 1993 July 2 (Box 128)
  - Tombstone, 1993 July 13 (Box 128)
  - Town Tamer, 1964 November 3 (Box 128)
  - The Track of the Cat, 1954 April 20 (Box 128)
  - The Track of the Cat, 1954 May 20 (Box 128)
  - Trail Blazers, 1940 September 4 (Box 128)
  - The Trail of Vigilantes, 1940 September 26 (Box 129)
  - The Trail Rider, undated (Box 129)
  - Trail's End, 1978 March 28 (Box 129)
  - Trail's End, 1978 May 16 (Box 129)
  - Trails West [Six-Shootin' Sheriff], 1938 (Box 129)
  - Train to Tombstone, 1950 July 21 (Box 129)
  - The Traveling Lady, 1952 August (Box 129)
  - The Treasure of Franchard, 1951 May 22 (Box 129)
  - Tribute to a Bad Man, 1955; 2 (Box 129)
  - Trigger Trail, [1944] (Box 129)
  - Triple Threat, undated (Box 129)
  - True Betrayal [Love and Lies], 1989 November 14 (Box 129)
  - True Confessions, 1978 December 27 (Box 129)
  - True Confessions, 1979 October 30 (Box 129)
  - True Grit, 1978 February 17 (Box 129)
  - True Stories, 1985 July 10 (Box 129)
  - Tucson Raiders, 1977 February 14 (Box 129)
  - Tulsa Kid, 1940 (Box 129)
  - The Tumbleweed Wagon, 1989 March 29 (Box 129)
  - Twilight for the Gods, 1958 April 28 (Box 129)
  - Twilight of Honor, 1963 February 6 (Box 129)
  - Twilight on the Rio Grande, [1947]; 2 (Box 130)
  - Twin Guns, [circa 1940] (Box 130)
  - A Twinkle in God's Eye, [circa 1954] (Box 130)
  - Two Bright Boys, 1939 August 19 (Box 130)
  - Two-Gun Lady, 1949 July 15 (Box 130)
  - The Two Jakes, 1989 April 7 (Box 130)
  - Ukiah, [circa 1918] (Box 130)
  - Ulzana's Raid, 1970 (Box 130)
  - Ulzana's Raid, 1972 January 11 (Box 130)
  - Unbeliever, [circa 1918] (Box 130)
  - Unconquered, 1946 June 29 (Box 130)
  - Unconquered [reels 1-8b], 1947 August 19; 15 (Box 130)
  - The Undefeated, 1962 May 11 (Box 130)
  - The Undefeated, 1963 July 15 (Box 130)
  - The Undefeated, 1968 November 22 (Box 130)
  - The Undefeated, 1968 December 3 (Box 130)
  - Under Mexicali Stars, 1950 July 11 (Box 130)
  - Under the Tonto Rim, 1933 March 1 (Box 130)
  - Under Western Skies, 1944 December 4 (Box 130)
  - Union Pacific, 1938 September 8 (Box 131)
  - Union Pacific [two copies], 1938 November 11; 2 (Box 131)
  - Untitled Western [Zebulon], undated (Box 131)
  - Urban Cowboy, [1980] (Box 131)
  - Vagabond Gaucho, undated (Box 131)
  - Valdez is Coming [two copies], 1969-1970; 3; Includes wardrobe records. (Box 131)
  - Valdez is Coming, 1969 September 1 (Box 131)
  - Valley of Hunted Men, 1942 August 19 (Box 131)
  - Valley of the Wild Stallion [Phantom Stallion], 1953 September 2 (Box 131)
  - The Vanishing, 1991 December 19 (Box 131)
  - The Vanishing Prairie, 1971 July (Box 131)
  - Vaquero [Ride, Vaquero!], 1951 November 5 (Box 131)
  - Vaquero [Ride, Vaquero!], 1952 February 11 (Box 131)
  - Vaquero [Ride, Vaquero!], 1952 April 11 (Box 131)
  - The Vigilantes, 1941 August 12 (Box 131)
  - Vigilantes of Dodge City, 1944 June 30 (Box 131)
  - The Vigilantes Return, 1947 January 24 (Box 131)
  - Virginia City [part 1], 1939 October 23 (Box 132)
  - The Virginian, 1944 May 11 (Box 132)
  - The Virginian, 1945 November 12 (Box 132)
  - The Virginian [The Brazen Bell], 1963 March 22 (Box 132)
  - Viva Max!, 1969 January 9 (Box 132)
  - W.W. and the Dixie Dancekings, 1974 February 5 (Box 132)
  - Waggoner, 1969 January 6 (Box 132)
  - Wagon Tracks West, 1943 May 3 (Box 132)
  - Wagon Wheels, 1934 September 11 (Box 132)
  - Wagons East, 1993 April 20 (Box 132)
  - Wagons East, 1993 April 20 (Box 132)
  - Wakely [Gun Law Justice], [1949] (Box 132)
  - Walk the Proud Land, 1956 May 23 (Box 132)
  - Wanda Nevada, undated (Box 132)
  - Wanda Nevada, undated (Box 132)
  - Wanderer of the Wasteland, 1935 June 14 (Box 132)
  - The Wanderer of the Wasteland [reels 1-7], 1935 August 24 (Box 132)
  - War Arrow, 1953 August 3 (Box 132)
  - War Drums, 1936 July 13 (Box 132)
  - War Paint, 1952 December 22 (Box 132)
  - War Party, 1985 August 22 (Box 132)
  - War Party, 1987 April 7 (Box 132)
  - The War Wagon, 1966 June 24 (Box 132)
  - The War Wagon, 1966 August 9 (Box 132)
  - Water, [circa 1975] (Box 133)
  - Way of a Gaucho, 1951 October 26 (Box 133)
  - The Way West, [1967] (Box 133)
  - Wayward Bus, 1957 January 17 (Box 133)
  - Wednesday Morning, undated (Box 133)
  - Welcome to Buzzsaw [Out on a Limb], 1990 August 12 (Box 133)
  - Wells Fargo, 1936 February 29 (Box 133)
  - Wells Fargo, 1937 June 17 (Box 133)
  - Wells Fargo, 1937 July 2 (Box 133)
  - Wells Fargo, 1937 July 2 (Box 133)
  - Wells Fargo [reels 1-6B], 1937 November 24 (Box 133)
  - West of Carson City, 1939 October 10 (Box 133)
  - West of Cimarron, 1941 October 20 (Box 133)
  - West of God's Country [Home on the Range], 1945 October 27 (Box 133)
  - West of the Brazos, 1950 February 11 (Box 133)
  - West of the Law [Santa Fe Trail], 1930 June 20 (Box 133)
  - Western Courage, 1950 March 22 (Box 133)
  - Western Jamboree, [1938] (Box 133)
  - Western Trails, [1938] (Box 133)
  - Westward Ho, 1942 February 26 (Box 133)
  - Westworld, 1973 February 27 (Box 133)
  - What a Day for a Hanging, [circa 1958] (Box 133)
  - Wheels of Destiny, 1934 (Box 134)
  - When the Daltons Rode, 1940 July 20 (Box 134)
  - When the Legends Die, [circa 1972] (Box 134)
  - When You Comin' Back, Red Ryder?, 1977-1978 (Box 134)
  - Where The Buffalo Roam, 1979 February 9 (Box 140)
  - Where The Buffalo Roam, 1979 May 23 (Box 140)
  - Where the Wind Dies [Passion], 1954 April 2 (Box 134)
  - Where the Wind Dies [Passion], 1954 April 19 (Box 134)
  - Where the Wind Dies [Passion], 1956 November 27 (Box 134)
  - Whip Law [Night Raiders], 1951 August 30 (Box 134)
  - Whirlwind Horseman, 1938 (Box 134)
  - Whiskey's Renegades [Sam Whiskey] [two copies], 1968 April 17; 2 (Box 134)
  - Whiskey's Renegades [Sam Whiskey], 1969 April 11 (Box 134)
  - The Whispering Skull, [circa 1943] (Box 134)
  - Whispering Smith, 1930 July 25 (Box 134)
  - Whispering Smith, 1948 March 9 (Box 134)
  - The White Dawn, 1972 October 13 (Box 134)
  - The White Dawn, 1973 April 21 (Box 134)
  - White Fang, 1936 March 25 (Box 134)
  - The Wild and the Innocent [The Buckskin Kid and the Calico Gal], 1958 July 10 (Box 138)
  - The Wild and the Innocent, 1959 February 20 (Box 134)
  - Wild and Woolfy, 1952 September 15 (Box 134)
  - Wild Beauty, 1946 August 15 (Box 134)
  - Wild Bill, 1994 January 11 (Box 134)
  - Wild Bill Hits the Trail, 1940 November 26 (Box 135)
  - The Wild Bunch, [circa 1955] (Box 135)
  - Wild Girl, 1932 July 29 (Box 135)
  - Wild Harvest, 1947 February 17 (Box 135)
  - Wild Harvest, 1947 February 17 (Box 135)
  - Wild Heritage, 1957 May 14 (Box 135)
  - Wild Heritage, 1958 June 24 (Box 135)
  - Wild Horse Mesa, 1932 October 2 (Box 135)